Close the border, and I want to drill, drill.
Let's have to go to a break.
I want to go back to this one issue, though,
because the media has been focused on this
and attacking you under no circumstances.
You are promising America tonight.
You would never abuse power as retribution against anybody.
Except for day one.
Except for?
He's going crazy.
Except for day one.
Meaning?
I want to close the border, and I want to drill, drill, drill.
That's not retribution.
I'm going to be...
I'm going to be, you know, he keeps...
We love this guy.
He says, you're not going to be a dictator, are you?
I said, no, no, no, other than day one.
We're closing the border, and we're drilling, drilling, drilling.
After that, I'm not a dictator, okay?
That sounds to me like you're going back to the policies
when you were president.
All right, take a break.
Just getting started.
We're in beautiful Davenport, Iowa.
Donald Trump with us for the hour as Hannity continues.
Thank you for being with us.